Today we are talking about how to put on a wig and what works and what doesn't.
If you have really long hair down to here, the best way to do that some people are afraid and they are like oh no I have way too much hair or my hair is way to long.
I can not possibly wear a wig.
But they are so much fun and you really should.
You can just braid your hair you know take a shower, braid your hair all the way down, then just flip it and put your cap on.
So you know once you have braided your hair completely, just put your cap on on top of your braid and it would hold it down.
It does not matter how long or how thick your hair is.
I have seen women with their hair down to their knees and they have worn wigs, we just condense it down.
Braided it and just put it inside the cap and very neatly in here.
Once you do that, you are going to do steps one 1,8,3,11 that we have showed your previously before.